Welcome everyone to today's product planning meeting. I'm glad we could all make it.
Let's start by discussing our roadmap for Q2. We have several important features to prioritize.
First on the agenda is the new dashboard redesign. Sarah, can you give us an update on the progress?
Sure. The design team has completed the mockups and we're ready to move into development phase.
Great. I think we should decide today whether to include the advanced analytics module in the first release.
After reviewing the timeline, I believe we can include it if we allocate two additional developers.
That makes sense. We've decided to go ahead with the analytics module in the initial release.
Perfect. John, can you create the technical specification document by Friday?
Absolutely, I'll have that ready. Should we schedule a follow-up next week to review it?
Yes, let's plan for Tuesday at 2 PM. Any other concerns or questions about the project?
One concern - we might face integration challenges with the legacy API. We should assess the risk.
Good point. Let's have the engineering team evaluate that this week and report back.
Alright, I think we've covered everything. Thanks everyone for the productive discussion.